Guide to the Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 1
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 1
Kheel Center for Labor- Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 1
5582
Kheel Center
80.1 linear ft.
Pamphlets.
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives, Cornell University Library
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
The Archives Foreign File is a collection of printed ephemeral documents, issued primarily by foreign and international trade unions and labor organizations. All continents are represented, though the majority of materials is of European origin. Topics covered in this collection include union organizing, unemployment, working conditions, the working class, the labor movement, industrial relations, worker education, international trade unionism, works councils, automation, economic conditions and trends, labor markets, foreign relations, and political movements, including fascism, socialism, and communism. Included in this collection are materials on the World Confederation of Labor and the World Federation of Trade Unions.
Due to the volume of material in this collection the finding aid has been divided into four sections.
Section 1: Boxes 1-22
Section 2: Boxes 23-44
Section 3: Boxes 45-66
Section 4: Boxes 67-79
Boxes 80-81 have not been inventoried at this time.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives
Subjects:
Labor unions; Labor unions--Political activity; Labor unions and foreign policy; Labor movement; International labor activities; Working class; Working class--Education; Industrial relations; Labor market; Unemployment; Economic history; Works councils; Work environment; Management--Employee participation; International relations; Labor unions and communism; Labor unions and socialism; Labor unions and fascism; Industrial safety; Industrial hygiene; Communism; Fascism; Socialism; Automation
Form and Genre Terms:
Pamphlets
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
RELATED MATERIALS
Other sections of this Collection:
5582: Archives Foreign File (AFF)
5582: Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 2: Boxes 23-44
5582: Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 3: Boxes 45-66
5582: Archives Foreign File (AFF), Section 4: Boxes 67-79
Boxes 80-82 have not been inventoried at this point.
CONTAINER LIST
- Box: 1, Folder: 1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: The Role of Trade Unions in the Newly Independent Africa, 1960; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Language: English.
  - Item 2: African Labor Disunity: Casablanca meeting affiliations, 1961; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Roland Gordon
    Notes: article
    Format: Publication
  - Item 3: African Democracy, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 4: African Socialism: A Sociologist's View, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: William H. Friedland
  - Item 5: African Socialism: an inter-disciplinary exploration, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Along the Road of Struggle for African Trade-Union Unity, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Josip Franic
  - Item 7: Discussion on the role of trade unions in the Newly Independednt Countries of Africa, 1960; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Stephen Low
  - Item 8: Labor in Africa, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Morton A. Reichek
  - Item 9: Major Issues of Wage Policy in Africa, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Elliot J. Berg
    Notes: Prelim for Conf use only
  - Item 10: Memorandum of Agreement made the Sixth Part, 1960; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author:
  - Item 11: North Africa Revisited (two articles), 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Lorna Hahn
  - Item 12: Strengthening U.S. - African Labor Links, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Paul Phillips and Max Greenberg
  - Item 13: The African Revolution, 1959; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: The Christian Science Monitor (several articles), 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Arnold Beichman
  - Item 15: The Christian Science Monitor (several articles), 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 16: The Christian Science Monitor (several articles), 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 17: The Problems of African Unionism, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Lester N. Trachtman
  - Item 18: This is the Voice of AATUF!, 1961; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 19: U.S. Communications Failure, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Richard Page
  - Item 20: Universities in Africa, 1961; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Notes: list
  - Item 21: Universities in Africa, 1961; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 22: South African Journal of Economics, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 23: Development of Collective Bargaining in Former British and Frend African Countries, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: B.C. Roberts & L. Greyfie de Bellecombe
  - Item 24: Problems of African Unionism, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Item 25: Africans of Nkana, 1949; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Rhokana Corporation
  - Item 26: Paradoxes of African Trade Unionism (two articles), 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: William H. Friedland; Dorothy Nelkin
  - Item 27: The African Labor College on the Equator, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Mark Starr
  - Item 28: Mission to East Africa, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 1)
    Author: Carl Schlesinger
- Box: 1, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Trade Unions in South Africa, 1954; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Author: Trades Union Congress
  - Item 2: The Economist and African Economic Development, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Author: Peter McLoughlin
  - Item 3: The Need to Study the History of Labor Policy in Africa, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Author: Peter F.M. McLoughlin
  - Item 4: The African University and Human Resource Development, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Author: Frederick Harbison
  - Item 5: Backward-Sloping Labor Supply Functions Africa Case, 1961; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Basic Social Trends in African Socialism, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Pan-African Trade-Union Organization, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Author: Dorothy Nelkin
  - Item 8: Socialism and Economic Development in Tropical Africa, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: South West Africa in the International Court: Act II, Scene 1, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Author: Elizabeth S. Landis
  - Item 10: The African Revolution and its Image in America, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Author: St. Clair Drake & Elizabeth Drake
  - Item 11: AALC: African-American Labor Center, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Author: African-American Labor Center
  - Item 12: AALC 1965-1973, Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Item 13: Visiting Friends in Free Africa with the FDGB and Ghana, 1960; Publication (Box 1, Folder 2)
    Author: Gunter Schabowski
- Box: 1, Folder: 3, Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Red Menace in Algeria, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 3)
    Author: Peter Braestrup
- Box: 1, Folder: 4, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: 1973 Workers' Target: The New Society, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Author: Central Latinoamericana de Trabajadores
  - Item 2: 20 Years of Struggle for Liberation, 1974; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 3: Excerpted from: US Congress House of Representatives, Committee on Foreign Affairs, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Braden Copper Company Minutes of Agreement, Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Notes: minutes
  - Item 5: Continue on the Road to Liberation, 1974; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 6: Economic Bulletin for Latin America, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 7: Economic Development of Central America, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Author: Committee for Economic Development
  - Item 8: Inter-American Conference of Ministers of Labor: Final Report, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Author: Pan American Union
  - Item 9: Latin America: Masses and Messiahs, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Author: Keith Botsford
  - Item 10: On Being 'Academic' South of the Border, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Author: Henry A. Landsberger
  - Item 11: Partners for Progress, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Author: Pan American Development Foundation Inc.
  - Item 12: Report on the Activities of the Latin American Institute for Economic and Social Planning, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Author: United Nations. Economic and Social Council
  - Item 13: The Pan-American Federation of Labor, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Author: Sinclair Snow
  - Item 14: The Role of the Trade Unions in the Alliance for Progress, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 15: The Workers Against the Challenges of the Capitalist Society, 1974; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 16: Thinking Aloud: For Progress after the Alliance, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Author: Thomas A. Gaines
  - Item 17: Inter-American Labor Bulletin (several articles), 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Author: varied
  - Item 18: Inter-American Situation Report (several articles), 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Author: multiple
  - Item 19: International News at the University of Pittsburgh, 1968; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 20: Latin America, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Item 21: Our America Yesterday and Today/Nuestra America Ayer y Hoy, 1960; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Author: OAS (Washington, D.C.)
    Language: English; Spanish.
  - Item 22: The Latin Labor Leader - Democratic and Dedicated, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 4)
    Author: Serafino Romnaldi
- Box: 1, Folder: 5, Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: The Labor Elite: Is it Revolutionary, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 2: The Labor Elite: Is it Revolutionary, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Notes: c.2
  - Item 3: Codigo de Trabajo de la Republica de Guatemala, 1961; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Author: Guatemala. Ministerio de Trabajo y Prevision Social
    Notes: 2 v. (only v.1)
    Language: Spanish.
  - Item 4: Conference on 'The Next Decade of Latin AmericanDevelopment', 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: America Latina y Los Congresos del Partido Comunista Ruso, 1959; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Author: Victor Alba
  - Item 6: La Confederacion de Trabajadores de America LatinaHistorica, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Author: Vicente Lombardo Toledano
  - Item 7: La Revolucion en Latinoamerica: Trascendental Figueres, 1959; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Author: Jose Figueres Ferrer
  - Item 8: Servicio Social de Grupo, 1956; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Author: Dorothea Sullivan
  - Item 9: Students on the March: The Cases of Mexico and Colombia, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Author: E. Wright Bakke
  - Item 10: The ORIT and the CLASC: A Case of Conflicting Perspectives, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Author: Carroll Hawkins
  - Item 11: Esta es la I.C.T.T., 1960; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
    Language: Portuguese.
  - Item 12: The Pan American Story, 1960; Publication (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Box: 1, Folder: 6, Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: New Hemisphere Labor Body Organized at Lima, 1948; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Spaniards and Englishmen: A Reconsideration of Colonization, 1959; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Author: Marvin D. Bernstein & Albert A. Blum
  - Item 3: Latin America (two articles), 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Author: Saul Mendelson & Victor Alba
  - Item 4: America Latina: Un Continente Ante Su Porvenir, 1958; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Unionism in Latin America, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Author: Miles E. Galvin
  - Item 6: Los Planes Obligatorios de Participacion en Latinoamerica, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Author: Carmel Mesa-Lago
  - Item 7: Contest of Papers on Scientific Administration, 1961; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Item 8: The Voice of Latin America - and its Significance in Today's World, 1961; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Author: William Benton
  - Item 9: Unity, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 6)
    Notes: v.6:no.2
- Box: 1, Folder: 7, Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: The Revolt in Angola, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 7)
    Author: John Marcum
- Box: 1, Folder: 8, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Hacia Una Mayor Productividad Del Trabajo, 1957; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Author: Wadim Struckhof
  - Item 2: La Izquierda Nacional en La Argentina, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Author: Alberto Methol Ferre
  - Item 3: Bill of Rights of the Workers, 1947; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Author: Juan Domingo Peron
  - Item 4: Peron Unmasked: The Martyrdom of the Free Tradein Argentina, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Author: ORIT (Organization)
  - Item 5: Peron Unmasked: The Martyrdom of the Free Tradein Argentina, Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: A Report to the AmericanArgentine University Situation, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Author: Latin American Studies Association
  - Item 7: Union Obrera Metalurgica de la Republica Argentina, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Notes: serial
  - Item 8: Union Obrera Metalurgica de la Republica Argentina, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 9: Union Obrera Metalurgica de la Republica Argentina, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: Estatuto, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Author: Union Obrera Metalurgica de la Republica Argentine
  - Item 11: Estatuto, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: Estatuto, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 13: Declaracion de Buenos Aires, 1961; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Author: Conference of American States Members of the International Labour Organisation
  - Item 14: Escuela Tecnica de Seguridad, 1945; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Author: Instituto Argentino de Seguridad
  - Item 15: Escuela Tecnica de Seguridad, 1945; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 16: Medicina Industrial Ergoiatria, 1956; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Author: Jorge Stavrinakis
  - Item 17: Vallese, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
    Author: Union Obrera Metalurgica
  - Item 18: Vallese, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Item 19: Vallese, 1963; Publication (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Box: 1, Folder: 9, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: El Sindicalismo en Transicion, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 2: Movimiento Obrero Argentino, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 3: Movimiento Obrero Argentino, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 4: La Estructura Legal, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: El Movimiento Obrero en Argentina, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: El Movimiento Obrero en La Argentina, 1965; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Confederacion General del Trabajo - Numero Adheridas, 1969; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 8: Movimiento Obrero Argentino - Conclusiones, Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 9: Power Struggle in Argentina, 1967; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Author: Henry Lee
  - Item 10: El Tiempo de la Ficcion, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: Salarios Basicos de Convenios, 1960; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Author: Argentina. Departamento de Estadisticas Sociales
  - Item 12: Convenios Colectivos de Trabajo, 1960; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Author: Argentina. Secretaria de trabajo y seguridad social. Departamento de estadisticas sociales
  - Item 13: Convenios Colectivos de Trabajo, 1958; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 14: Movimiento Obrero Argentino - Una nueva etapa para el sindicalismo, 1943-1955 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Item 15: Argentina's Durable Peronists: A Twentieth Anniversary Note: Part 1, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 9)
    Author: James W. Rowe
- Box: 1, Folder: 10, Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Informe Sobre Las Actividades Reakizadas A Partir, 1971; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 2: La Plata, noviembre de 1972 (letter), Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Julio Cesar Neffa
    Notes: correspondence
  - Item 3: Sindicalismo en America Latina, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Almino Affonso
  - Item 4: Sindicalismo en America Latina, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Luis Pasara; Jorge Santistevan
  - Item 5: Sindicalismo en America Latina, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Raul Bission; Floreal H. Forni; Julio Cesar Neffa
  - Item 6: Sindicalismo en America Latina, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Chi-Yi Chen
  - Item 7: Sindicalismo en America Latina, 1972; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 8: Argentina Federation of the Tobacco Industry: Cigarette Branch: Work agreement with the Syndicate of Tobacco Employees: Collective Convention No. 95/59, 1959; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
    Author: Argentina Federation of the Tobacco Industry; Syndicate of Tobacco Employees
  - Item 9: Argentina Federation of the Tobacco Industry: Cigarette Branch: Work agreement with the Syndicate of Tobacco Employees: Collective Convention No. 95/59, 1959; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Item 10: Relaciones del Trabajo, 1957; Publication (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Box: 1, Folder: 11, Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Cultural Continuities and Discontinuities in Southeast Asia, 1962; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: Lauriston Sharp
  - Item 2: Jennie Lee to Jim Loeb (personal correspondence), 1946; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: corres.
  - Item 3: Looking at Southeast Asian History, 1960; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: D.G.E. Hall
  - Item 4: State and Industrial Relations, 1964; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: Charles Gamba
  - Item 5: Asian Trade Union College, 1956; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: Asian Trade Union College, Calcutta
  - Item 6: Dawn Over Asia, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 7: Dawn Over Asia, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 8: West Meets East, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 9: West Meets East, 1952; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Item 10: The ILO, Asia and Pakistan, 1966; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Author: David A. Morse
  - Item 11: Asian Seminar on Workers' Education, 1958; Publication (Box 1, Folder 11)
    Notes: Conf. Program
- Box: 1, Folder: 12, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Metal Trades Federation, Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Notes: by-laws
  - Item 2: Rules (Federated Miscellaneous Workers' Union of Australia), Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Author: Federated Miscellaneous Workers' Union of Australia
  - Item 3: Rules (Trades and Labor Council of Queensland), Publication (Box 1, Folder 12)
    Author: Trades and Labor Council of Queensland
- Box: 1, Folder: 13, Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Rules (Vehicle Builders Employees Federation of Australia), 1940?; Publication (Box 1, Folder 13)
    Author: Vehicle Builders Employees' Federation of Australia
- Box: 1, Folder: 14, Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: Rules (Hobart Trades Hall Council), 1926; Publication (Box 1, Folder 14)
    Author: Hobart Trades Hall Council
- Box: 1, Folder: 15, Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Regulations for the Management/Laws and RulesHall Council, 1935; Publication (Box 1, Folder 15)
    Author: Trades Hall Council (Melbourne, Vic.)
- Box: 1, Folder: 16, Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 1: Labor in Australia: The story of a successful labor movement, 1943; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
    Author: Lloyd Ross
  - Item 2: Labor in Australia: The story of a successful labor movement, 1943; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Item 3: Labor in Australia: The story of a successful labor movement, 1943; Publication (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Box: 1, Folder: 17, Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 1: Historical Background of the World Labor Movement, 1943; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Author: E.W. Campbell
  - Item 2: Rules (Amalgamated Engineering Union), 1942; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Author: Amalgamated Engineering Union (Australia)
  - Item 3: Rules (Amalgamated Engineering Union), 1942; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Item 4: Constitution (Australasian Council of Trade Unions), 1941; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Author: Australasian Council of Trade Unions
    Notes: seiral
  - Item 5: How to Reduce Absenteeism and Increase Australian Survey, 1943; Publication (Box 1, Folder 17)
    Author: Australia. Department of Labour and National Service
- Box: 2, Folder: 1, Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: Labor Unions in the Far East; Working PeopleStandards, 1945; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Notes: tossed. Kheel already has 4 copies
  - Item 2: Arbitration and the Engineer, 1948; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Author: Institution of Engineers, Australia
    Notes: lecture
  - Item 3: Australian Workers' Union, 1947; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Author: Australian Workers' Union
  - Item 4: The Graziers' Association of Victoria, 1949; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Author: Graziers' Association
  - Item 5: Regulations for the Management/Laws and RulesHall Council, 1946; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 6: Regulations for the Management/Laws and RulesHall Council, 1946; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 7: Jobs, Freedom, Progress, 1948; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Author: J.B. Miles
  - Item 8: Rules and Standing Orders (United Trades and Labor Australia), 1945; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Author: United Trades and Labor Councils of South Australia
  - Item 9: Metal Trades Award (Metal Trades Federation), 1948; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Author: Metal Trades Federation of Unions (Australia)
  - Item 10: Rules (Australian Textile Workers' Union, 1948; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Author: Australian Textile Workers' Union
  - Item 11: Federal Construction Award (Australian Workers Union), 1949; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 12: Federal Fruitgrowing Industry Award of 1949 (Australian Union), Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 13: Federal Pastoral Industry Award (Australian Workers' Union), 1948; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Item 14: Constitution and Platform (Australian Labor Party), 1949; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Author: Australian Labor Party
  - Item 15: Rules (Transport Workers Union of Australia), 1948; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Author: Transport Workers' Union of Australia
  - Item 16: Rules (The Labor Council of New South Wales), 1946; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Author: Labor Council of NSW
  - Item 17: Rules (The Australian Leather & Allied TradesFederation), 1949; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
    Author: Australian Leather and Allied Trades Employees' Federation
  - Item 18: Constitution and General Rules (Australian Workers Union), 1949; Publication (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Box: 2, Folder: 2, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Industrial Awards in Force - Titles, 1953; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 2: Procedure for the Handling of Disputes UnderGoverning Industry, 1952; Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Commonwealth Cases: Dismissals, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Australian Stevedoring Industry Board, Publication (Box 2, Folder 2)
    Author: Australian Stevedoring Industry Board